乔伊 这就是你父母 叫你不要在床上跳的原因
See, Joe, that's why your parents told you not to jump on the bed.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 纵有狂风暴雨 #
# When the rain starts to pour #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 支持一如往昔 #
# Like I've been there before #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
看看我 我在做果酱
Hey, look at me. I'm making jam.
我早上四点就起来了
I've been at it since 4:00 this morning.
那么早你怎么可能买得到水果
Where'd you get fruit at 4 in the morning?
在码头那边买的
Went down at the docks.
你一定不知道能买到批发价
Bet you didn't know you can get it wholesale.
我根本不知道有码头
I didn't know there were docks.
嘿
Hey.
你手断了吗
Aw, is it broken?
不 但得挂着这东西几个星期
No, but I gotta wear this thing for a couple weeks.
你有没有告诉医生你是因为在床上跳才受伤
Did you tell the doctor you did it jumping up and down on your bed?
不 我编的故事本来行得通的 但是…
No. I had a whole story worked out, but then...
钱德出卖了我
...Chandler sold me out.
抱歉 乔伊
I'm sorry, Joe.
我想医生不会相信你说手臂就自己断了
I didn't think the doctor was gonna buy that it just fell out of his socket.
这是什么水果吗
What is this? Fruit?
摩妮卡在做果酱
Monica's making jam.
我最爱果酱了 我们家怎么从来没有果酱
Jam? I love jam. Hey, how come we never have jam at our place?
因为孩子们需要买新鞋
Because the kids need new shoes.
我得做正事了 我不想再为理查的事烦心
I'm going into business, people. I'm sick of being depressed about Richard.
我需要一个计划来忘记我的男人
I needed a plan. A plan to get over my man.
什么是男人的反义词 就是果酱
What's the opposite of man? Jam.
乔伊 别动 太烫了
Joey, don't. It's way too hot.
那么这就算我的了
This will just be my batch.
到此止步 嘿 你这位穿名牌的…
Um, that's it. No. Hey you. J. Crew guy...
你干嘛跟踪我
Yeah. Why are you following me?
这一周来 我在哪里都能看到你
All week long, everywhere I look, there's you.
你不回我电话 又把我的信退回来
You wouldn't return my calls. You sent back my letters.
- 什么    - 再给我一次机会 乌苏拉
- What?     - One more chance, Ursula. Please.
真是太尴尬了
Oh. Well, this is awkward.
怎么了
Why?
你要找的是乌苏拉 而我是菲比 我们是双胞胎姐妹
Yeah, because you want Ursula, and I'm Phoebe. Twin sisters.
我认真的
Seriously.
真不好意思 我跟错人了
Oh. That's great. I'm stalking the wrong woman.
我真是个傻蛋
I am such a dingus!
你不是傻蛋
Oh, you're not a dingus.
我只想让你知道我不是一直这样的
I just... I want you to know I didn't used to be like this.
在认识你姊姊之前 我只是
Before I met your sister, I was, like, this normal guy...
卖手机的普通人
...who sold beepers and cellular phones.
听着 这不是你的错 知道吗
Well... I mean, look, it's not your fault, you know?
只是她对待男人就是这个样子
I mean, this is just what she does to guys, okay?
就是…
Just...
谢谢
Well, thanks.
等等 我有个小故事告诉你
Wait. You know what? I got a little story.
我在念国中时
When I was in junior high school...
有一阵子 我以为自己是女巫
...I went through this period where I thought I was a witch.
有个辅导员老师跟我说了一段的话
And there was this guidance counselor who said something to me...
我想可以帮助你
...that I think will help you a lot.
他说 "你根本不是女巫 你只是个普通学生"
He said, "Okay, you're not a witch. You're just an average student."
- 你懂我的意思吗   - 不是很懂
- See what I'm saying?     - Not really.
忘了这段感情吧
Um, well, get over it.
你看起来是个好人
I mean, you just... You seem like a really nice guy.
别太难为自己 好吗
You know, I just... Don't be so hard on yourself, okay?
没错 你说得没错 谢谢你对我这么好
Wait, you're right. I know you're right. And thanks for being so nice.
给你
Here.
谢谢你
Thanks a lot.
你要不要去喝杯咖啡
Do you wanna get a cup of coffee or...?
- 好啊   - 好
- Yeah, okay.     - Okay.
你不用走在我后面了
You don't have to walk behind me anymore.
抱歉
Sorry.
- 摩妮卡  - 摩妮卡
- Mon?     - Mon?
"去多买些罐子 等一下回来 摩妮卡•盖勒"
"Gone for more jars. Back later. Monica Geller."
等等 你看
Wait a minute. Look.
- 看看…   - 怎么了…
- Look, look, look.     - What, what, what?
整间公寓里都没人
- It's an empty apartment.     - Mm.
这间空房里只有我们两个
We're all alone in an empty apartment.
我十分钟后得去上班
Aw, honey, come on. I have to be at work in, like, 10 minutes and, oh...
好吧 我又不是模范员工
All right. Well, it's not like I'm employee of the year or anything.
在这里啊
There it is.
这就是你要找的
Oh, that's what you're talking about.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
我看起来很胖吗
Do I look fat?
不胖
No.
这么说我可以接受
Okay, I accept that.
当珍妮丝问我时 我回答不
When Janice asked me and I said no...
她却认为我说她像母牛
...she took that to mean that I was calling her a cow.
重头再说一次给我们听…
Okay, walk us through it, honey. Walk us through it.
珍妮丝说…
Okay, well, Janice said, uh:
"我今天看起来胖吗 我看看她…
"Hi. Do I look fat today?" And I looked at her...
你看看她
You looked at her?
你绝不能看
You never look.
你只能回答 就像条件反射 "我看起来胖吗" "不"
You just answer. It's like a reflex. "Do I look fat?" "No."
"她比我漂亮吗" "不"
"Is she prettier than I am?" "No."
- "尺寸很重要吗   - 不
- "Does size matter?"     - No.
这点男女都适用
And it works both ways.
所以你们本来就知道这些
Okay, so you both just know this stuff?
吵了大概三四十次架后 你大概就了解了
You know, after about 30 or 40 fights, you kind of catch on.
例如
Okay. For instance, ahem:
珍妮丝旅行回来 她给你两种选择
Let's say Janice is coming back from a trip and she gives you two options.
选择一 她从机场自己搭计程车回来
Option number one: She'll take a cab home from the airport.
选择二 你在领行李的地方与她碰面 你会怎么做
Or option two: You can meet her at baggage claim. What do you do?
简单 领行李的地方
That's easy. Baggage claim.
错了 这样你就没女朋友啦
Ehh! Wrong. Now you're single.
其实是第三个秘密绝招
It's actually secret option number three.
你在接机门与她碰面 这就表现出你对她的爱
You meet her at the gate. That way she knows you love her.
好 这样真不错
Okay, this is good. This is good.
好 我有一个问题 珍妮丝喜欢抱抱…
All right, listen, I have one. Janice likes to cuddle...
在晚上的时候 我当然也喜欢抱抱
...at night, which I'm all for.
不过当你想睡觉时 你会想要一点空间
But, uh, you know, when you want to go to sleep, you want some space.
我要怎样告诉她 才不会…
So, uh, you know, how do I tell her that without...
不小心又说她胖之类的
...you know, accidentally calling her fat or something?
抱歉 我们帮不了你 因为我们都是抱着睡的
Oh. Honey, I'm sorry. We can't help you there, because we're cuddly sleepers.
我上班要迟到了
Okay, I'm late for work.
- 你们要不要下来   - 好 等一下就去
- Are you guys gonna come down?     - Uh, yeah. I'm right behind you.
- 祝你好运 钱德   - 谢了 瑞秋
- Good luck, Chandler.     - Thank you, Rachel.
- 再见   - 再见 宝贝 亲爱的
- Bye, sweetie.     - Bye, honey.
关于睡觉那件事
Okay, the sleeping thing.
非常困难 但也不是没办法可想
Very tricky business but there is something you can do.
- 我以为你们都是抱着睡觉   - 其实不是
- I thought you were cuddly sleepers.     - No.
不 不是抱着睡 不是我 只有她
No, not cuddly. Not me. Just her.
我跟你一样 我需要空间
I'm like you. I need the room. Ahem.
好 到这里来
Okay, come here. Ahem.
好 现在你在床上
Okay. You're in bed.
好吧
Yeah?
- 我还是用靠垫好了   - 好吧
- I'm gonna use the cushion.     - Yeah.
好 你在床上 她在你旁边 抱着你
Okay. You're in bed. She's over on your side cuddling.
现在 你等她逐渐睡着…
Now, you wait for her to drift off...
然后你抱住她…
...and then you hug her...
然后把她滚到床的另一边
...and roll her over to her side of the bed.
然后你…
And then you...
你就滚到一边去
...roll away.
抱住她
Hug for her.
滚到一边去
Roll for you.
- 就像以前的拥抱与翻滚   - 对
- Okay, the old "hug and roll."     - Yep.
- 只有一个问题   - 说吧
- Okay. One question.     - Shoot.
你把枕头当作女生 对吧
You're pretending the pillow's a girl, right?
记得小时候…
Remember when you were a kid...
你妈会把你送到电影院…
...and your mom would drop you off at the movies...
给你一罐果酱和一根小汤匙
...with a jar ofjam and a little spoon?
你真可爱
You're so pretty.
- 嘿   - 嘿 菲比
- Hi.     - Hey, Phoebe.
你知道那个跟踪我的人吗 我今天跟他说话了
Hey, oh! You know that guy who's been following me? I talked to him today.
你跟他说话 你疯了吗
You talked to him? Are you crazy?
第一 我没有疯 第二 用嘴来说 别乱喷
Okay, first, I'm not crazy. And second, say it. Don't spray it.
反正他叫做麦肯 他也不是在跟踪我
Anyway, his name is Malcolm, and he wasn't following me.
我是说 他在跟踪没错 但他以为我是乌苏拉
I mean, he was, but just because he thought I was Ursula. Ick.
所以他不敢上前来跟我说话
And that's why... That's why he couldn't just come up and talk to me.
因为有禁制令
Because of the restraining order.
我还是对麦肯没有好感
Hmm. Not feeling better about Malcolm.
不 他不是疯子
Oh! No, no, no, he's not like a kook.
他只是个非常热情 极度浪漫的家伙…
No, he's just this, like, very passionate, incredibly romantic guy...
只是有点过火了
...that just got a teensy bit carried away, you know?
我们处得很好 而且他很可爱
And we just get along really well, and he's so cute.
天啊 你竟然喜欢跟踪你姊姊的人
Oh, my God. You've got a crush on your sister's stalker.
我要帮他忘记乌苏拉的一切
No, I'm just gonna help him, you know, get "de-Ursula-ized."
就像乔伊跟她约会后我为他做的一样
Like, you know... Like I did for Joey after he went out with her.
我没有跟踪她
Yeah, but I didn't stalk her. I mean...
你是鸡同鸭讲
I asked for the news, not the weather.
- 嘿 大伙儿   - 嘿 摩妮卡
- Hey, guys.     - Hey, Mon.
乔伊 这是你的 这是黑莓红醋栗酱
Joey, this is for you. It's blackberry currant.
太美妙了
Yeah.
乔伊 我得问你
Hey, Joe, I gotta ask.
影印店的那个女孩 全裸
The girl from the Xerox place, buck naked...
还是你要一大缸果酱
...or a big tub of jam?
你把两只手放在一起好了
Put your hands together.
你慢慢吃啊 那是最后一批
Joey, take your time with that. That's my last batch.
没有果酱了
No more jam?
你的果酱计划呢
What happened to your jam plan?
我算过了 我每罐得卖17元才能打平
Well, I figured out I'd need to charge 17 bucks a jar just to break even.
所以我有个新计划 就是生小孩
So I've got a new plan now. Babies.
那你可能需要很大的罐子
Well, you're gonna need much bigger jars.
- 你在讲什么   - 讲我要要生小孩的事
- What are you talking about?     - About me having a baby.
- 你是认真的吗   - 是的
- Are you serious?     - Yeah.
果酱计划让我开始掌握自己的生活
The great thing about the jam plan was I was take control of my life.
所以我就想什么事对我最重要
So I asked myself, "What is the most important thing to me?"
因此我就想出生小孩这个计划
And that's when I came up with the baby plan.
你是不是忘了什么
Well, aren't you forgetting something?
那个家伙叫什么 叫"爹地"
What is, uh...? What is that guy's name? Dad.
我花了28年找到一个想与他共度终身的男人
It took me 28 years to find one man that I wanted to spend my life with.
如果我还得再等28年 我就得56岁才生小孩
If I have to wait another 28 years, then I'll be 56 before I can have a baby.
那样实在太愚蠢了
And that's just stupid.
那样叫愚蠢
That's what's stupid?
我不需要一个真正的男人 只要他几个会游泳的小家伙
I don't need an actual man. Just a couple of his best swimmers.
而且你可以在某个地方弄到那些小家伙
You know? And there are places that you can go to get that stuff.
又要去码头了吗
Down at the docks again?
晚安 大宝贝
Night-night, Bing-a-ling.
晚安
Night-night...
珍妮丝
...Janice.
看看她那一边的空间
Look at all that room on her side.
都可以放一只大企鹅了
You could fit a giant penguin over there.
不过那样会很奇怪
That'd be weird, though.
要开始拥抱与翻滚了
Hug and roll time.
我正在拥抱…
I'm hugging. I'm hugging.
你在翻滚 然后…
You're rolling, and...
太好了 自由了
Yes! Freedom!
除了这只胳膊
Except for this arm.
我被困住了 胳膊卡住了
I'm stuck. Stuck arm.
该玩以前那种抽桌布的游戏了 一个华丽得快动作
Okay, time for the old tablecloth trick. One fluid motion.
像猫一样敏捷
Quick like a cat. Quick like a cat.
一 二
And one, two...
三
...three.
这是我的望远镜
Here's my binoculars.
很好 你做得很好
Oh, great. Great. You're doing great.
很不错 继续吧
You know, real strong. Going strong. Keep going.
这是我的夜视镜
These are my night-vision goggles.
这是我在公园里看她时假装阅读的书
This is the book I pretend to read when I'm watching her in the park.
这些是接字游戏 只是打发时间用的
And these are Madlibs. They're just for fun.
噢 好吧 这是什么
Oh, yeah. Ha, ha. What's this?
这是我写的日志 记录她的一举一动
Oh. This is the log I kept, recording her every movement.
- 要不要听听看   - 我一点也不想听
- You want to hear something from it?     - Um, not even a little bit.
- 是跟你有关的   - 那好吧
- It's about you.     - Oh, okay, then.
"我今天遇到菲比
"I met Phoebe today.
她对我很好 即使我是个窝囊废
She was really nice to me even though I'm such a loser."
当我走回家时 我不断想着她
"And then when I was walking home, I thought about her a lot.
虽然很怪 但是很酷"
It was weird but kind of cool."
很好
Good. Ha, ha.
你在想什么
So, what were you thinking?
我在想亲你是什么感觉
I was thinking what it'd be like to kiss you.
- 真的   - 开玩笑
- Really?     - No.
我是故意说的 这样我才能亲你
See, that's just something I said now so that maybe I could kiss you.
噢 好吧
Oh, okay.
不 不用了 我刚吃了一罐芥末
No, it's all right. I just had a jar of mustard.
好 捐精者编号03815
Okay. Sperm donor number 03815, come on down!
好 他是6尺2寸 170磅
Okay, he's 6'2", 170 pounds.
他形容自己是男性的吉娜•戴维丝
And he describes himself as a male Geena Davis.
你是说除了我们之外还有别人
You mean there's more than one of us?
你不能这样做 摩妮卡 如果你这么做 我会…
You can't do this, Mon, all right? If you do this, I'm gonna...
- 你能怎样   - 我会告诉妈
- You're gonna what?     - I'm gonna tell Mom.
很抱歉 他是对的 我爱你 可是你真的疯了
Honey, I'm sorry, but he's right. I love you, but you're crazy.
- 疯了   - 为什么 这样就疯了
- Crazy.     - What? Why? Why is this crazy?
- 就算这不是最理想方法   - 这根本不是…
- So this isn't the ideal way to do something...     - Oh, it's not...
别打断 我还在讲话
Lips moving. Still talking.
这样可能不太理想 但…
It may not be ideal...
我真的准备好了
...but I'm so ready.
我看到班看着你的样子
You know, I see the way Ben looks at you.
让我心好痛 你知道吗
It makes me ache, you know?
你看看 果酱饼干
Check it out. Jam crackers.
好吧 这个如何
Okay. All right, how's this?
27岁 意大利裔美国人
Twenty-seven. Italian-American guy.
他是个演员
He's an actor.
在皇后区出生
Born in Queens.
大家族 七个姊妹 而且…
Wow. Big family. Seven sisters...
他是唯一的男孩
...and he's the only boy.
天啊 个人评论写着 ""纽约尼克队"最厉害"
Oh, my God. Under personal comments: "New York Knicks rule."
对啊 "纽约尼克队"最厉害
Yeah, the Knicks rule.
乔伊 这个是你
Joey, this is you.
让我看看
Let me see.
哦 对
Oh, right.
你什么时候去过精子银行
When did you go to a sperm bank?
就在我参加纽约大学的性研究之后
Right after I did that sex study at NYU.
你记不记得你生日时我送你的毛衣
Hey, remember that sweater I gave you for your birthday?
那是你用这样赚来的钱买的
And that's how you bought it?
不 那是我捐精子那天穿的
No. That's what I was wearing when I donated.
我真惊讶他们那里还会有我的小家伙
I'm kind of surprised there's any of my boys left.
那里竞争很激烈的
Well, honey, it is pretty competitive.
还有真正的火箭科学家呢
I mean, I've got an actual rocket scientist here.
或许我该叫他们
Hey, maybe I should call this place...
把我演的"我们的日子"放上去
...and get them to put my Days ofour Lives gig on here.
多增加点声势
You know? Juice this puppy up a little.
- 嘿    - 你好
- Hey!     - Hello.
那个疯子如何了
How's the maniac?
他真迷人 我们接吻了
Oh, he's yummy. We did a little kissing. Aah!
菲比 你在搞什么
Phoebe, what are you doing?
不 你们知道吗
Oh, no, no, no. You know what?
不 他不会再犯了 他为了我戒掉了
He's not into that anymore. He quit for me. Mm-hm.
那家伙迷恋你姊姊
Pheebs, this guy has been obsessed with your sister...
天晓得到底有多久了
...for God knows how long, okay?
他不可能就这样忘了她
You don't just give up something like that.
他把他的夜视镜和一切东西都交给我了
Look, he gave me his night-vision goggles and everything.
一个有夜视镜的人说的话你也敢信
You're taking the word of a guy who has night-vision goggles?
他不再跟踪她了 你觉得他还在跟踪她吗
What? He's not still following her. You think he's still following her?
快醒醒 感觉一下什么叫禁制令吧
Pheebs, wake up and smell the restraining order.
你说我该怎么办
What should I do?
若你真的很喜欢他 应该相信他才是
I think that if you really like this guy, you should just trust him.
谢谢你 摩妮卡
Thank you, Monica.
也许你该跟踪他 看他会去哪里
Or you could follow him and see where he goes.
我也会这么做的 忘了我刚说的吧
Oh, that's what I would do. Forget mine.
天啊 发生什么事
Oh, my God. What happened?
钱德发神经 把我转一圈…
Oh, God. Crazy Chandler, he spun me...
然后推下床
...off the bed.
转圈圈啊 听起来很好玩
Wow. Spinning. That sounds like fun.
我倒希望
I wish.
他只是在试罗斯的那招 拥抱与翻滚
No, you know, he was just trying Ross' "hug and roll" thing.
罗斯的什么
Ross' what?
当他抱住你把你滚到旁边  再…
You know, like, where he hugs you and then he kind of rolls you away, and...
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
- 菲比   - 怎样
- Phoebe?     - Yes? Yes! Oh.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我只是在找我的…
Oh, I was just here looking for my, um...
吃过的三明治 在这里
My part of an old sandwich. Here it is! Oh!
你在跟踪我吗
Were you following me?
也许
Um, perhaps.
是的 我很抱歉
Yes. Yes. I'm sorry.
我害怕你仍然迷恋我姊姊
I'm sorry. I was just afraid that you were still hung up on my sister.
所以你在监视我
So you spied on me.
我真不敢相信你不信任我
I can't believe you don't trust me.
你知道什么 我的双胞胎姊姊正好经过
Oh, well, what do you know? There goes my identical twin sister.
就这么走着 跟我长得一模一样
Just walking along, looking like me.
这是个奇异的巧合 还是你早知道她会搭这班车
What is this, just a freakish coincidence, or did you know that she takes this train?
对不起…
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我试着停止 但我做不到
I tried to stop, but I couldn't.
我真可悲
I'm so pathetic.
不 不是你的错 我也有错
No, no, it's not your fault. You know, it's partly my fault.
是我要你断然戒除这个毛病
It's because I made you quit cold turkey.
这很难 你知道吗
It's too hard, you know?
我不能再跟你约会了 因为你是…
Okay, well, I mean, I can't date you anymore, because you're, you know:
但我一定要帮你忘掉我姊姊
But, um... But I will definitely, definitely help you get over my sister. Okay?
试着跟踪我一阵子 好吗
Just stalk me for a while, huh?
我就暂时帮你戒除对乌苏拉的迷恋
Yeah, and I'll be like an Ursula patch.
我不知道
Uh-huh. I don't know.
你就…你看 我正在走路
Yeah, just... Okay, look, I'm going.
来吧
Um, come on.
我遇到柱子了 我会往哪边走
Ooh, ooh, behind the pillar. Ooh, which way am I gonna go? Aah!
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 上哪里去   - 银行
- Where you going?     - To the bank.
精子银行还是一般的
Huh. Sperm or regular?
精子银行
Sperm.
你确定要做这件事
So you're really doing it, huh?
是啊 我挑了一个男性 编号37135
Oh, yeah. I picked a guy, 37135.
听起来不错
He sounds nice.
的确 他有棕发和绿眼睛
I'd say so. He's got brown hair and green eyes.
不是开玩笑吧
No kidding? Hmm.
- 怎么了   - 我以为你会选金发的
- What?     - I figured you'd have picked a blond guy.
真的吗为什么
Really? Why?
我总是想像你和…
I don't know. I always pictured you ending up...
一个高大聪明的金发男子 叫…
...with one of those tall, smart, blond guys, name like...
荷依
...Hoyt.
- 荷依   - 这是个名字
- Hoyt?     - It's a name. Yeah.
我看到你在一间很棒的有泳池的大房子
I saw you in this... You know, this great house with a big pool.
他是游泳选手吗
Yeah? Is he a swimmer?
他可是有那种身材的
He's got the body for it. Ha, ha.
我喜欢
I like that.
- 怎样   - 你们有这样的标语…
- Ha, ha. What?     - You guys have one of those signs that says:
"我们不在你的厕所游泳 所以别在我们的池子尿尿"
"We don't swim in your toilet, so don't pee in our pool."
我们才不会有那种标语
We do not have one of those signs.
你会有的 那是我送的礼物
Sure you do. It was a gift from me.
然后你会有三个很棒的孩子
Oh! And you have three great kids.
- 两个女孩和一个男孩   - 没错
- Two girls and a boy?     - Yeah!
他们戴着浮水圈
And they wear those little water wings, you know...
绕着泳池边跑
...and they're running around on the deck.
然后荷依用毛巾围住他们三个
And then Hoyt wraps this big towel around all three of them.
没错
Sure.
但是 你知道这样听起来也不错
Uh, but, hey, you know, this way sounds good too.
是啊
Yeah.
喔 摩妮卡
Oh, Monica.
这家伙是太空人
Wow, this guy's an astronaut?
这样虽然很棒…
That would have been cool...
也不会维持多久
...for, like, a day. Ah-ah!
我打电话给精子银行
I called the sperm bank today.
我的小家伙一点也没卖出去
They haven't sold a single unit of Tribbiani.
没有人要我的产品
Nobody wants my product.
我真是不了解
I mean, I don't get it, you know?
我的意思是…
I mean...
如果她们能亲眼见到我
...maybe if they met me in person.
你沾到一点果酱在…
Uh, honey, you got a little thing on your...
- 哦   - 是的
- Oh.     - Yeah.
弄掉了吧
Get it?
是啊
Yeah.
哈罗
Hello.
嘿
Hey.
钱德 我可以跟你谈一下吗
Chan, can I, uh...? Could I talk to you for a second?
当然 什么事
Sure. What's up?
还有一件关于男女之间的事
Just one, uh... One additional relationship thought.
这件事你大概已经知道了
Um, something you're probably, uh, already familiar with.
女人会互相讲八卦的
Uh, women talk.